let us look at an example of VCG in
让我们来看一个VCG的例子
action of the victory park roads
胜利公园道路行动
mechanism in action and it'll be a
作用机制，它将是一个
rafting transportation problem so here
漂流问题，所以在这里
is a directed network of links each link
是链接的定向网络，每个链接
had the cost of the length of it if you
如果你有长度的代价
wish and the goal is to find a shortest
希望，目标是找到最短的
path from A to F and obviously looking
从A到F的路径，显然
at it I'll be quite obvious that the
在这一点上，我会很明显地看到
shortest path is this one and so this is
最短的路径就是这个，所以这是
the path that would be selected by a
由a选择的路径
traveler who wishes to get there from A
希望从A到达那里的旅行者
to F most quickly now according to a BCG
根据BCG，现在最快地到达F
how much would the owner of the link AF
链接AF的所有者要多少钱
pay well intuitively he's not part of
凭直觉支付好他不属于
the other path so we shouldn't have to
另一条路，所以我们不必
pay or receive anything let's see what
支付或接收任何东西，让我们看看
VCG says so the shorter path with a C's
VCG说，所以C的较短路径
declaration of what their cost is is
声明其成本是
five right and so the cost to all the
五权，所以所有的成本
agents is that shortest path totaling
代理商是最短的路径总计
five had AC not being in the picture and
有五个人不在照片中
not declared anything therefore what if
没有声明任何东西，如果
what would the total cost to the agents
代理商的总费用是多少
have been well it would have been the
很好，应该是
very same path so the shortest path and
路径完全相同，所以最短路径和
so the cost would have been five also
所以成本也将是五
and so the amount that AC pays if you
因此，如果您
wish is the difference between the cost
希望是成本之间的差异
to the agents within the picture and the
给图片中的代理商和
cost without him in the picture which of
图片中没有他的代价
course is zero and this is true for all
当然是零，这对所有人都是正确的
the other ages other edges that don't
其他年龄的其他优势
participate in the shortest path all
全部参加最短路径
these edges
这些边缘
draw in blue these edges not
将这些边缘涂成蓝色
participating the shortest path will
参加最短路径将
will neither pain or seep anything
既不会痛苦也不会渗入任何东西
according to BCG so that's the easy part
根据BCG的说法，这很容易
what about edges that do participate in
那么参与的边缘呢
the shortest path so let's look for
最短的路径，让我们寻找
example at one of them at a B well with
例如在一个B井中
the shortest path as we know is it is
我们知道的最短路径是
this one and how much would all agents
这个和所有代理商多少钱
other than a B itself what is the cost
除了B本身，成本是多少
of the agents on the shortest path well
最短路径上的代理商
it's 1 plus 1 is 2 cost of two had a B
它的1加1是2的成本，两个有B
not being in the picture what would have
不在图片中会有什么
happened well the shortest path would
发生得最好的最短路径
have been um this one over here so this
一直在这一个这里，所以这个
would have been the shortest path of a
本来是一条最短的路
cost of 2 plus 3 plus 1 and so the cost
成本2加3加1等等
to the agent a B is the difference
与代理商A B的区别
between the cost without them in the
在没有它们的情况下
picture which would be minus 6 and the
图片将是负6和
cost with them in the picture which is
与他们在图片中的成本是
minus 2 that is a cost to all the other
减2是其他所有费用
agents and the difference is minus 4 so
代理和差是负4所以
the crust to a B is minus 4 in other
B的外壳在其他地方为负4
words a B will get a payment of four
单词B将获得四的付款
making if you wish a profit of 1 because
如果您希望获利1，
their cost is 3 we'll get a payment of 4
他们的成本是3我们将支付4
and they'll have a benefit of 1 so this
他们将受益1
is for a B what about B II for example
对于一个B例如B II
well the same sort of analysis
同样的分析
ve the cost to all other agents without
将所有其他代理商的费用
being the picture is minus six it's
图片是负六
still this would have been the shorter
仍然会更短
route had been on in picture and cost
路线已经在图片和费用中
would be minus six now the cost to the
现在将是负六
agents with be in the picture to the
与代理商在图片中
agent rather than be e is for why is
代理而不是e是为什么
that it's one plus three and so the cost
那是一加三，所以成本
to this is the minus four over here so
这是这里的负四
the net of it is that the cost imposed
最终的结果是所施加的成本
on by VCG on the link be e is minus two
由链接上的VCG开启，e为负2
in other words they would get a payment
换句话说，他们会得到付款
of two making again a profit of one if
的二分之一再次获利，如果
you wish
你希望
what about EF same same of calculation
EF与计算相同
although the outcome would be a little
虽然结果会有点
different because in that case they will
不同，因为在这种情况下，他们会
be getting a payment of three why is
得到三分钱，为什么
that well without them in the picture
没有他们在照片中很好
this would no longer be the shortest
这将不再是最短的
path the shortest path would be a cost
最短的路径将是成本
of 7 whether it's this one or this one
的7，无论是这个还是这个
in both cases the cost of the first path
在这两种情况下，第一条路径的成本
will be 7 so the total cost to the
将为7，因此总费用为
population without them in the picture
图片中没有他们的人口
would be 7 with them the cost is again
和他们在一起将是7
the 1 plus 3 it's a 4 and so they get
1加3是4，所以他们得到
the difference of 3 so the payment would
3的差额，所以付款
be 3 and therefore the net profit if you
为3，因此净利润为
wish it would be 3 minus 1 name namely 2
希望它是3减1的名字，即2
so you could ask why are why is it the
所以你可以问为什么是为什么
difference you know you look at all
差异，你知道你看看所有
these links somehow their net payoff is
这些链接的净收益是
different and that's fair
不同，这很公平
and what fairness is in the eye of the
眼中的公平是什么
beholder but the rationale for it is
情人，但其理由是
that they have different market power
他们有不同的市场力量
the amount of social value they bring is
他们带来的社会价值是
different because without them the
不同，因为没有他们
outcome will be different into the
结果会有所不同
population and that's why they have a
人口，这就是为什么他们有一个
different sort of payments and different
不同的付款方式和不同的
cost structures here that's an example
成本结构就是一个例子
of BCG in operation
运营中的BCG